<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DataViz Makeover on Su Yiin&#39;s blog</title>
    <link>https://suyiinang.netlify.app/posts/dataviz_makeover/</link>
    <description>Recent content in DataViz Makeover on Su Yiin&#39;s blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://suyiinang.netlify.app/posts/dataviz_makeover/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>DataViz Makeover #3</title>
      <link>https://suyiinang.netlify.app/posts/dataviz_makeover/03_makeover/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suyiinang.netlify.app/posts/dataviz_makeover/03_makeover/</guid>
      <description>Political Violence and Protests in South East Asia This was written as part of the requirements for the Visual Analytics module for MITB.
 For this DataViz Makeover, I have used data from The Armed Conflict Location &amp;amp; Event Data Project (ACLED), a centralized hub for data on all reported instances of political violence and protests around the world.
1. The original visualisation  var divElement = document.getElementById(&#39;viz1615905508827&#39;); var vizElement = divElement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DataViz Makeover #2</title>
      <link>https://suyiinang.netlify.app/posts/dataviz_makeover/02_makeover/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suyiinang.netlify.app/posts/dataviz_makeover/02_makeover/</guid>
      <description>Understanding the willingness of public for Covid-19 vaccination based on survey data. This was written as part of the requirements for the Visual Analytics module for MITB.
 1. The original visualisation For this DataViz Makeover, I have used data from Imperial College London YouGov Covid 19 Behaviour Tracker Data Hub, which collects global insights on people&amp;rsquo;s behaviours in response to Covid-19.
Figure 1
Before making over the selected visualisation, it is important to have a clear understanding of the context of the visualisation and its key takeaways which are dependent on:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DataViz Makeover #1</title>
      <link>https://suyiinang.netlify.app/posts/dataviz_makeover/01_makeover/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suyiinang.netlify.app/posts/dataviz_makeover/01_makeover/</guid>
      <description>Making over a chart from the Singapore Labour Force (2019) report. This was written as part of the requirements for the Visual Analytics module for MITB.
 For my first DataViz makeover, I have used data from the Ministry of Manpower of Singapore, which analyses Singapore’s labour force to understand shifts in the labour market to facilitate better decision making.
1) The original visualisation Figure 1: Chart 6 of Labour Force in Singapore 2019 report (page 22)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
