<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Academic Projects on Su Yiin&#39;s blog</title>
    <link>https://suyiinang.netlify.app/posts/a_projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Academic Projects on Su Yiin&#39;s blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://suyiinang.netlify.app/posts/a_projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Taking a Shot at COVID-19 Vaccine Hesitancy on Reddit</title>
      <link>https://suyiinang.netlify.app/posts/a_projects/08_text-mining/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suyiinang.netlify.app/posts/a_projects/08_text-mining/</guid>
      <description>Categories: text-mining, reddit, vaccine-hesitancy, sentiment-analysis, topic-modelling
a Textual Analysis via Topic Modelling &amp;amp; Sentiment Analysis By Bernard Lim, Su Yiin Ang, Anne Nyugen Nhi Thai An, Ron Tan, Pengjie He, Poh Wai Wong.
This was written as part of the requirements for the Text Analytics and Applications module for MITB.
 1. Introduction As of April 2021, the Covid-19 pandemic has caused 135 million infections, 2.9 million deaths and repeated resurgence due to mutated variants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shiny prototype test for Exploratory Analysis</title>
      <link>https://suyiinang.netlify.app/posts/a_projects/07_ourshinypet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suyiinang.netlify.app/posts/a_projects/07_ourshinypet/</guid>
      <description>Categories : R Shiny, Exploratory Analysis, Confirmatory Analysis, ggplot, airbnb
This was written as part of the requirements for the Visual Analytics module for MITB. Update: This application is now live, visit our
 Website Application Poster Paper   1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understanding the Stars</title>
      <link>https://suyiinang.netlify.app/posts/a_projects/06_airbnb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suyiinang.netlify.app/posts/a_projects/06_airbnb/</guid>
      <description>Categories: SAS JMP, SAS Enterprise Miner, Airbnb, text-analysis, exploratory-analysis, confirmatory-analysis
Augmenting Numerical Data with Textual Analysis to Identify Key Determinants of Airbnb Review Scores By: Ang Su Yiin, Anne Nguyen Nhi Thai An, Toh E-Lynn
This report was written as part of the requirement for the Data Analytics Lab module for MITB.
 For poster, please view : Poster{target=&amp;quot;_blank&amp;quot;}
1. Abstract Text analytics provides powerful tools for transforming large amounts of unstructured data into quantitative variables, allowing researchers to contribute unique insights to business decision-making.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post-COVID Recovery for SIA</title>
      <link>https://suyiinang.netlify.app/posts/a_projects/05_sia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suyiinang.netlify.app/posts/a_projects/05_sia/</guid>
      <description>Categories: excel, modelling, SIA, spreadsheet
Optimizing Passenger-Cargo Fleet Allocation By: Ang Su Yiin, Gabriella Pauline Djojosaputro, Gordy Adiprasetyo, Kendra Luisa Baylon Gadong, Nguyen Nhi Thai An, Ulysses Chong Min Zhen
This was written as part of the requirement for the Spreadsheet Modeling module for MITB.
 For executive report, please view: Executive Report{target=&amp;quot;_blank&amp;quot;}
1.	Problem Statement With the halt of international travel due to COVID-19, the global aviation industry is one of the industries that was hit the worst.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Predicting H1N1 Vaccination</title>
      <link>https://suyiinang.netlify.app/posts/a_projects/04_predict/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suyiinang.netlify.app/posts/a_projects/04_predict/</guid>
      <description>Categories: predictive, regression, decision tree, SAS Enterprise Miner
This was written as part of the requirement for the Data Analytics Lab module for MITB.
 Predicting H1N1 vaccination based on flu survey. For executive report, please view: Executive Report - Predicting H1N1 vaccination{target=&amp;quot;_blank&amp;quot;}
1.	Introduction The H1N1 outbreak in April 2009 swept across the world and caused a global pandemic. CDC estimated that the H1N1 virus claimed the lives of 151,700 – 575,400 people worldwide during its first year of circulation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Math of Happiness</title>
      <link>https://suyiinang.netlify.app/posts/a_projects/03_asar/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suyiinang.netlify.app/posts/a_projects/03_asar/</guid>
      <description>Categories: R Shiny, regression
The Math of Happiness: An analysis of factors that influence happiness. By: Ang Su Yiin, Anne Nguyen Nhi Thai An, E-Lynn Toh, Foo Kai Loon, Sean Samuel Prajs, Tay Kai Lin
This was written as part of the requirement for the Applied Statistical Analysis with R module for MITB.
 Shiny app available at The Math of Happiness{target=&amp;quot;_blank&amp;quot;}
1. Introduction The quest for happiness is an elusive pursuit for many.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Market segmentation of Philippines’ market</title>
      <link>https://suyiinang.netlify.app/posts/a_projects/02_segmentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suyiinang.netlify.app/posts/a_projects/02_segmentation/</guid>
      <description>Categories: market segmentation, k-means, latent class, clustering, SAS JMP
This was written as part of the requirement for the Data Analytics Lab module for MITB.
 Market segmentation of Philippines’ market based on expenditure patterns of households. For executive report, please view : Executive Report - Segmentation{target=&amp;quot;_blank&amp;quot;}
1. Objective This report aims to group the Philippines’ consumer market into target segments based on similar spending patterns on hypermarket items using clustering methods in JMP.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hotel booking cancellations</title>
      <link>https://suyiinang.netlify.app/posts/a_projects/01_hotel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suyiinang.netlify.app/posts/a_projects/01_hotel/</guid>
      <description>Categories: exploratory, confirmatory, hotel booking, SAS JMP
This was written as part of the requirement for the Data Analytics Lab module for MITB.
 An analysis of guests’ booking and cancellation trends for two Portuguese hotels. For executive report, please view : Executive report - hotel booking{target=&amp;quot;_blank&amp;quot;}
1. Overview Changing Landscape of the Hotel Industry
According to D-Edge, the rise of online travel agents (OTAs) has caused hotels in Europe to experience a shift in distribution channel mix – in particular, from the websites of hotels, to OTAs (particularly Booking.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
